(Leonard:)Something you're excited about even
though it could give you diabetes.
(Penny:)Sweetie, you can be
any pastry you want.
(Leonard:)No, no. No, it's too late.
I'm your bran muffin.
(Leonard:)Probably fat-free
and good for your colon.
(Penny:)You know what? Forget it.
I never should've brought it up.
(Leonard:)You know I want to marry you,
but you're only doing this
(Leonard:)because you got fired
and you're feeling sorry for yourself.
Okay, it may lock that way,
but getting fired
(Penny:)from that movie was the best thing
that could have happened to me, okay.
(Penny:)I finally realize
I don't need to be famous
(Penny:)or have some big career to be happy.
(Leonard:)-Then what do you need?
-You, you stupid Pop-Tart!
(Penny:)Oh.
(Leonard:)Then I guess I'm in.
(Raj:)Really?
You guess you're in?
Not like, "I guess I'm in."
Like "I guess I'm in!"
Okay. Cool.